Oh
People such a headache, you know, we got Arthur whining. Oh
Yeah, all these people are just arguing me. Hey, just don't say it I
Know I just like I want to restart it because I'm like, well, don't say any like you saying it saying it over and over
And over like I meant anything you won't like you keep saying saying it like
And it's like he's making like death threat. I mean, it's like, yeah, I don't what are you doing?
There's not a place to do your death threats, you know, there's a lot of public place in your dream public
Yeah, now it's like you're yeah, I know I think nobody wants to see that
You're not welcome on panel anymore until you can like behave yourself calm down. I ask you not to say that that word
Yeah, the restart show. Yeah
Yeah, but any other people on the panel because it's like, you know, it's like all of a sudden, you know, you know
the panel is like just
It's not should never be a lot on again. You don't think so
Yeah
Well, come on guys somebody else come on the panel it won't come on the panel and chat, you know
What happened? Oh, they're just like he does those things. I was like, don't say this and then he kept saying it
This is a lot of there's some language I didn't like the last so
You know
Yeah, I was just kidding I was getting watching squid games and I was just getting very boring
They were just arguing back and forth and back. I don't know what they're arguing about
Another thing he resets on the panel
I don't know when there's people that want to come on the panel that like a clue
Just let me know if you want to come on the panel
Right now as I drop in the link just for anybody to come up. They get this
Starts the same thing over again. I think
Yeah, I got this associated it's getting repetitive. Yeah, I don't mean I don't even know what to be for the bow. I just think you know
At least I like to be left out of
Oh, Doug, come on. Doug, I'm sorry, Diggie, let's fix it.
Um, well, I don't know, yeah, it was just like, you know, people, I don't know, he's saying crazy things.
He knows not to say those things. I don't know. I really, I really had a problem with it.
I don't know, it was just, uh, who's the guy? Um, Diggie was just, like, saying horrible things.
Anybody hear that
Everyone's okay. How's everyone doing today? I love you guys. So you guys
Yeah, I don't know what's good, so it's not a different storyline than Ziggy saga
Not too interesting to me. I don't like he is like
Demonic, since you lived for too long
The day went well awesome, HG
I'm trying to show up for Aldi. Yeah
He got like oh Aldi. Oh, isn't that kind of gay like wanting to show up for another guy
Post the panel. Oh, I'll do what what all the all do wants to come up here and say the f-a-g-g-o-t and then
Yeah, you just want to come back up and like start trouble guys
See he's banned from betas for horde racist remarks
Oh
I don't know
Convince convince me. I just let you on the panel you guys are like not members
Yeah
I'm not on it by now, probably never be on it, I streamed a lot.
Hey there, I know, well, I know it's hard to speak, I mean, I'll have the, I have the
panel backed up, I just don't want to like...
Ziggy, I think he's a break because he was like he was like now he's making death threats
He was talking out of control. I mean even all do is better better better behaved. And so all a lot of it is like
We'll see what happens. I don't that you guys, you know
Just pretend you're a church almost like you pretend you're like it like a church
maybe like we're even if we're like, you know, it's like, you know, the you know, the
You have hot luck or something like that. You know, we can run our own corner and
We can say whatever we want
like let's just pretend like you know even because it's in search like pretend it's a
it's a what we're we're just we're gonna behave ourselves like what we
you're going to I know you're just you know you're really you're gonna help you're gonna
help me out today right I'll be
hello what's up you fucking bitch
why are you being so fucking censored sexy
You look good. What have you been? You've been in the gym. I like good. I look sexy. What have you been doing?
Thank you. I haven't been doing anything.
Gym, psych. No, no.
No, I'm just, I'm always in the same skinny bag as them.
You've been a little slut. You've been horning around like a little slut. Huh? That's what I've been hearing.
Really? What did you hear?
I heard that you've been a little slut.
You've been a little freaky little slut on Grindr
and just moving around a lot.
A lot different now.
Now that you got all this hype and stuff,
I heard that you've been a little freak.
It's kinda sexy.
Okay, well, I don't think so.
I know, I'm watching it.
I'll be kicked, okay.
You know, all the ones to like...
because
Hi, I'll be how are you? How are you? You're saying you're really nice today
What's up, how are you?
Sweet oh, I'm pretty good
Yeah, well good to see you again anything to promote any interesting anecdotes or
Yeah, but what brings you here? You're serious? I've been getting a lot of like sponsorship deals and stuff for my stream
No, yeah
So I just been hanging out and stuff. I got a new PC from one of my sponsors. Oh, nice
I've got a headset and like
Mouse keyboards a couple controllers
Some clothes and stuff. It's been really cool man. Um, yeah, like
Yeah, streaming has been really taken off recently man. Like what have you been doing man?
Well, well, oh gosh
Ziggy if you come on you can't talk about those showing off for Aldi like, you know, don't try to be cool
You know, it's like, you know, we know Aldi's cool and we know you're not you're uncool
So just not even like try that and no talking about unaliving people. Okay?
Or else I'll kick you off. Okay. Yeah
Alright, yeah. No, I mean, no, you are cool. I would are cool
The like yeah, I did get our relationship and now I'm looking into the relationship with psyche. That's it. Oh, you are
Oh wait, what did you say? You're not with me
No, no, I didn't say I'm in love. I can't be in love
I'm saying I just got out of relationship and that's why those girls were there and
No, you know, hey
You know, okay, but your other things out, you know, okay, okay
Right, you think all these I
Don't know I think he's just trying to be funny. He's trying to make fun of you being gay
All right, all right, you are yeah, I think it's no no being gay and he's trying to be funny for the chat
Has always been a huge bitch, dude fuck this guy. No, you have always been no you
Your mom like even one of me need tacos man. What the hell dude?
Crazy
You're crazy, you know, you're crazy
You're crazy
What do you think now psych after hearing
Hello
See it's kind of weird isn't it it's kind of weird hearing like a
It's all weird. It's absolutely weird. Yeah, because it's weird is um
Okay, I'm going to run soon. Let's not forget. Thank you for allowing this shit to drag me into his room. I'm just kidding
Are you mad at me? Oh, you come on. Yo, you come on piano. I don't know. I'm not sure. I
Have miles bottom. If there's anything going on the chat or if there's something going on like let me know
I just don't I just don't know like you know people talk, but yeah, you're not allowed to talk about him on these don't
You see
Yeah, I don't know. Ziggy don't want it. I didn't do anything. I didn't do anything about it. Okay, but I don't know what he's talking about
He just leave the stream
I drive him into his room. Let's see. I don't know. Okay. So that one's three people. Hey all the and see
I don't know. You're ready boy. I'm going to fuck up
dish
No, they're trying to say that no, I know what they're doing. They're trying to say that me and Audi are like
Bows and we're not like I don't like Audi like fuck him
That's I don't know. I don't know what he's talking about. I don't think he's talking about you
But guys, if anybody knows this, what's going on in the chat, he's got his guys kind of like
I've never known this guy ever. So Audi, I don't know who the hell you are, but you're
you're making my life hell. That's what you're doing. Hold on. Okay. I know a way to fix
this shit. What? How do you do? I want I want you and psych to have a conversation and then
I'm okay. Is that a way to fix it? It's perfect, right? Yeah, that's great. That's great.
Is Princess coming? I'll talk to you later. Bye. Bye.
Is Princess coming? Bye, sweetie.
Bye. See, you didn't pour on me.
No, no, he's not gonna pour on me, man. No. No.
No, he's with uh, you know, he's with a special guy
Okay, the guy you see someone. Oh, yeah, like we're all kind of that you know
Let's be honest here
You're what?
Honest, let me be honest here. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, well we're that way. Yeah, okay
I mean
We don't call it that way, but like Rusty would say that, you know
What do you say? You're saying you're that way like like well sees day with Dan, right?
Oh, and yeah, you know, you say oh, so you're gay with Aldi like you would you would have sex with Aldi
Oh, I would have I mean how do we do it? You know, I kind of I've seen all watching all these all these balls
And so, you know
A couple of you guys have you ever seen all these balls?
All right, I thought you were in
this area. Send it to me on
Discord. You can send me your
picture of your balls.
Hello?
I'll be here.
Sorry, I was getting off.
Oh, my bad.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
Well, perfect.
I'll take all the out. I'll do the left
on his own.
Oh
Are you ever gonna reveal your face like are you like you know, are you good-looking are you like 500 pounds?
They are what I want to like I could probably track down your dick pick if I
Don't know what you're saying. I got how do you look like are you are you ever gonna show your face on a on camera?
Are you always? Oh, oh you want what I'm not gonna do on camera again because I've already done it like a night time
Let's see
What are you chewing on you're all you're that's weird you're constant. It's like how it's like the jalapeno
Oh, it's our more nails man. It's the jalapeno at the bottom of this
Let's see, where am I at?
That's me.
Let me see, hold on.
Oh, wow.
Pretty cute.
There we go, guys.
I don't like it though, I like it.
No, I mean, no, don't don't say it don't say here we go guys. No, how about how about a how about a picture of you with your shirt off?
Yeah, no, what are you like doing like a flexing a flexing photo you flex like I'm not flexing anything
What are you wearing? Well, what are you in there? Are you wearing a hockey outfit? Oh, what is this outfit?
What's that? What it says? You're wearing it. Hold on. You're wearing it. You're wearing a beanie. I mean
Again, very easy. I mean, it's like you're very very it's very small. Okay, you know
You're wearing a beanie or a hat and then you're wearing a oh a beanie for sure. Yeah, I've dreads. Yeah
You have dreadlocks. I can I can do like the
Okay look and then I can do the you know
Yeah
Okay, and so and so are you fit or you know, you can just a really oversized I mean
In pretty fit a hockey jersey. You look like you're like you look like kind of surprised enough or like, oh, you know
Expression
Yeah
You're touching what are you you're touching your belly there like you know, you're like, I'm hungry. I'm hungry
No, no, no, no, it's me and like I'm like
Your stomach having a baby your stomach hurt at the time. I'm having a baby. Okay, baby. You're pregnant, baby
You were born a female, okay
I was okay. I think it's ten years old look at the old old. Yeah, that that iPhone
I remember that I didn't iPhone that 2006 wasn't that like when that iPhone came out. I don't know
Well, no, no, I did
Seven iPhone six seven. I don't know
Thank you
This is one of the earlier
It's kind of big. Okay. It's okay. It's okay. Um, let's see. Well, I'm glad you're here. Yeah
Okay, well no flexing no no muscle. I mean, it's hard to see I mean, but thank you for sharing your oh
Just the two of us it is just the two of us. Okay. Oh, just the two of us
You and I
Can you play it and make it? No. Can you actually play it? I can sing it. I can sing it
I hear the rainbow raindrops fall and the beauty of it all and I want to spend some time with you
Just the two of us
We can make it if we try just the two of us just the two of us
Making a tree trial that sucks building castles in the sky. Just this two of us
Ziggy and I know Ziggie looks like an extra in the background of a hoodie and and then
Okay, do it again do it again like
Sometimes I see the raindrops fall. I don't have to look up the lyrics on
Do you mind if I look at the lyrics? I can see it perfect
No, I was going to do the back vocals.
Just a two verse.
Ha ha ha ha.
That doesn't sound good.
Guys, who's in the read further chat?
Let me see. Good.
I see the crystal rain drops fall
and the beauty of it all
is when the sun comes shining through.
Make those rainbows in my mind when I think of you some time and I want to spend some time with you
Okay, how's that I don't know yeah, I don't like it
That was good. Yeah, that was great. Yeah, thank you
No, yeah, what do you like always chewing on what is this?
What is it
Oh
Sub
No, it's a pizza. I mean, you know, I actually have some some sub left. I have my sub left
There it's really good. Oh, I thought it was the sub like, okay
You know my nail kid is the tail already
Hey
What?
Check me mine. This is fine. She's right here
So the shit no, there's a dog. Yeah, I don't see
Don't talk about here
And you have to go and like take care of okay, and they kick you off
You're being disrespectful. I don't like the way you're talking. I don't like don't use like language about like army animals
I'm sorry. I'm oh
didn't know
You didn't know
Like I felt like that if there's a dog barking you should go and discipline it that's all like it like a woman
You should discipline it and
But it they can't be possible. I know
Right. Yeah, I would change. Yeah, okay. Let's change this up. Yeah
Topics changed. We got beta in the chat y'all wiggum. How are you?
Elevator elevator it is my boy. He's not a good boy
He's a good boy I
Eat some salami and cheese today. Yeah, what are you doing beta?
Hey, Sebastian
Sebastian's here. Oh, no. Now he's going to offer people weird stuff. Vader's cool, though. I love Vader.
My God.
Is it that good? What the hell?
It was that good?
Hey, wait, hold on, wait, before you do anything, you said, yeah, it was delicious.
I didn't mention it, Tard, I, I, uh, I can't believe I'm also a woman to a dying, like,
You
Tommy are we ain't too bright the best of the give us create the trashmanic who's I don't know who I'm sorry
I don't know who people
Just reading comments, and I don't mean to
Oh, no, what's your shit? I mean you can read whatever the hell you I know but I just don't know
I just don't want to be bearded comments. I guess I don't know. I don't want to be involved in all this other drama
Sebastian was if there's guys that there's Sebastian if Sebastian was doxing mods because I have some mods
And he just like delete those comments and like Sebastian if you can't stop doxing
Who is that that him who is that I
Didn't I didn't I don't like people just bringing up pictures
Who is that see type of the back to who that is
Who is that yeah, I think you know, please I don't I don't want people
Yeah, why is everyone so weird? Oh
You're not weird you're the magic of moment. Okay, but what yeah, yeah, that's so rude. Okay. He changed his back
What's that about? Oh, that was me. Oh, that was me dumb dumb. That was you
Yeah, okay. Show you
All right, what?
That's me right here
That's you on
Yeah, but yeah, oh
I thought it was a woman. Okay. Okay
I thought it was a woman.
You're interesting.
I like your perm.
It's awesome.
Are you in the shower there?
It's not perm.
It's dreads.
So you're trans.
I didn't know you were trans.
I'm not trans at all.
What do you mean?
Oh, you're not. Hold on. Hold on. That's what Samantha said. Samantha, hold on.
Oh, that's my tattoos and stuff. I love my tattoos. I really love them.
You're making kind of like a woman's, like a woman's experience.
I don't know what I'm doing. Yeah, I don't know.
Are you wearing pants in that photo?
Was I what?
And
We're in the shower it closed right in the shower
How am I in a shower? No, I was no I was in a
I don't even know where I was to be honest, but it wasn't a shower. I don't remember
Are you on the toilet?
Hey, yeah, there you go. I'm on a toilet. Yeah. Yeah
That's the woman's tank top like you know that shape of it. I think that's
Okay, hell yeah
Didn't look like a normal way. Is it tank top?
Yeah, it does have that. I don't even know what I'm wearing. Are you here? Oh, yeah, are you in a gay bathhouse?
right
Thompson that's someone else. I don't know where I'm at right there really who later says definitely a shower
Are you home from work?
Mm-hmm. Okay. Okay. What do you guys think? Oh, that's him too. Wow. Look at this is God's face. He has dark eyes
I don't know. I have no idea. I don't even know where I was it might have been like a friends house or like I'm
Maybe my mom's or something. I don't even remember
So I turn the situation around
Yeah, well, and I think you're pursuing your pictures, you know, you look pretty pretty hot in some of the photos some of the photos
I don't know. I mean, I'm
I'm interested though and
Are you ready? Do you want to come spend the weekend with me?
No, you can have the bed. I'll just like, you know, join you in there a few if you ask me to
You ain't talking to
Oh
Hey, Bud heads, what are you doing?
Why are you doing? Hi?
Look a ladybug. Oh my gosh. How cute. Come here little guy. Look it. I
Found a baby bug. Look I grab her brother. Make a wish
I'm not going to eat the ladybug, I'm just kidding, he fell, he's good.
Let me see, let me see if I can tell about the ladybug, we just saw a ladybug, so let's
see, maybe that's a little sign, we can always look up ladybug.
He's on my arm now again, you won't go away, look.
Oh no.
Cruisin', he's cruisin', I should race ladybugs for a side hustle.
That'd be so lame.
Okay.
And here's some Mrs. Legend of Ladybugs.
It says,
Self-closures believe ladybugs carry away illness if they land on your own flyaway unassisted.
Counting spots will tell you a number of good things and how many months of good fortune one will have in the coming year,
how many children the person holding it will have, or how much money one may expect to gain.
They are often seen as symbols of keeping safe and healthy, which is why ladybugs often appear on
clothing. To some farmers, an abundance of ladybugs in the spring signifies political crops
And to others, they indicate forecast of fair weather.
And it says, mm, OK, that's what they're called.
I just want to say, before I go away, Paige,
you look very pretty.
Thank you
I want to I want to you know recharge my phone and for another girl her name is
Tiffany worse t-shirts like I think she's
Do not harass her I saw I saw a JT was harassing her last night. No, he's like one of my friends. What do you mean? Okay? Okay?
So Tiffany, let me know if this guy's
Yeah, and so I know you're part of that group and so I hope you're not making a group. I don't know why you keep calling me a group.
You and Rain and Jody.
No, I thought I was in your group. What do you mean?
Well, we're all in the same group, so sometimes we have groups beforehand. We have many groups.
No, I don't know. Don't don't don't don't pick me up. I'll pick on Tiffany
Okay, thank you. Thank you. Thank you for having me. Tiffany's great and amazing. Good night page. Good night
Person must be put some clothes on. Oh shit, I knocked you guys over. Let's see
I'm not doing it. No, I actually put a coat on though because it's fucking kind of cold over here
Look at it. It's so pretty. It's empty
No golfers because it's shitty weather right now, but it's okay
Can't do nothing about it there try that
Hi, what are you doing?
Oh my gosh, so I had to drive one of my co-workers home and he's got like he's got like
Like ten cats and they're they have babies and it's like all the kittens and stuff
there's like little tiny ones and then medium ones and all kinds of different ages and
I was going to leave and one of the little cats had pooped on the like by my sandal
I went to put it on I put my foot in shit that I had to come to work. Oh my god. It was brutal
Anyways, I had kitty poop on my foot today, so I'm catching it
That's okay. They're so tiny. They were so cute. I just love them. They could just barely walk some of them. So
Hey daughter of truth in the chat
Yeah, well, I have I'm sitting here with tricks and the Norse right here. Hey, the North you had a pagey. Hey
Hello everybody in the chat
So I get to I brought Grace to work today. She's cruising around on the golf cart checking all the like all the whole buckets
To see if there's cans and stuff. She's pretty old. She helped him with you
Okay, that's the drive the golf cart and if she likes to help me cook and she likes to help with the tail and just he likes
Helping she's a really good girl
People came in today and I'm like is that your little sister. I was like, no, that's my kid. They're like shut up
But she does kind of look like that when she was really little I did not like she looked more like her dad and not me at all
It looks like I stole her or I was her babysitter
But she looks like yeah, yeah, I would I thought they're fucking annoying man. Who wants to steal an annoying kid?
That's just my personal opinion
I didn't even want to have kids and then obviously that changed but when I was younger I didn't was like nah
They're all booger pickers and droolers
Well
You know, I don't know my you know
My my or one of my family's I'm happy with cats. Oh, yeah, I'm not just someone over. Hey, baby
I'm happy
What's the bash it was going on in the
What who's who's fighting in the cat? What are you fighting about?
Sebastian you're fighting with Tom. Why are you fighting with Tom?
Well Sebastian when you were on last night Sebastian you talked about some very controversial topics. I'd luckily, you know everything was okay
You know, but you know in the future, you know
I'm gonna try not to leave you alone the show, but if I do, you know, try to be a little
little less controversial
Yeah, so the mask of more. Oh, yeah
Dave
There's Lenore. Hi Lenore.
Yeah
Some uh
Pizza bagels. Hey
Pizza bagels. Yeah, I just had to make a shit ton of food for people that were in here. I made like
Wings and burgers and poutine and all that. Oh, yeah, you guys don't have poutine
I should have totally felt myself making that so I could show you how to assemble a poutine
It's the easiest thing in the world
And we don't use the expensive cheese curds either. We'd have to charge like $20 for a poutine
Yeah, how we listen to me or I'm gonna put you in a bucket
So do you see page there's the new thing in chat where they could the top chatters like guys
Who's in who's the top three chatters today, and they have like little awards. They get
Yeah
It's a YouTube thing it's a YouTube thing and that's the it goes YouTube
Other Doug D's here
let's see that's funny you tell
let's see live i kind of want to do a panel later i was thinking about maybe
doing it but i also like i haven't decided yet
you said you said yeah i don't know if i know enough on like
that end i just want to be on the panel because i'm on yours all the time but
like i don't i don't beat us and other people's but i don't know how to like
Well, all you do is like, you know started through shimmy art. I think it says you've been approved through it and stuff
So you can right that night that we did it. I got approved the next day. I just yeah
And so yeah, just that you just uh, you know open it to open shimmy art go shimmer.com
You know it says, you know you create a title
It will just think you know connect your YouTube account and then it will start streaming from shimmy art
Your YouTube account would think that would think that you know the ability to bring people on panel
Yeah, I know you okay. I know I know you're fine. No, no, it's gonna kick page. Come on Patrick Peterson. Oh my gosh
Who's who's this person Patrick Peterson? Oh, you don't like me too fucking bad. I ain't going anywhere
Yeah
He's uh, he's just damning guys. Is there a mod in the chat? Oh, yeah, there is. Okay. Thank you so much
You're getting kids watching out
Fuck
Kick page. Okay. Well, you can if you want to I don't really care about like hard up about it
But he was spamming he was spamming. I don't think anyone's gonna
Everyone look at now. We have it people are coming out in different accounts doing it. Oh my gosh
So I've only got a spam bot or something a
Spam bot
Yeah, who would do such a thing I mean come on
It's a waste of time
Rick, I don't know what to do today. I washed carts, but they all got rained on anyway
Quit bouncing that and following me around. I'm gonna take it away
Fashion you were doxing. What were you doing?
Guys who paid for something guys? Why would you pay for it guys? That's ridiculous. Okay guys
I'm gonna hop back on to my shift, but I will message I've messaged you later
What the fuck who am I talking to I will talk to you guys in a little while I'll get another break
I just gotta do something here. Love you, P. G. Oh
Bye-bye
I'll be back in like ten minutes
Okay
I have a mic outside. I still can't hear you. I hear you.
Uh, so, uh, Sacko again?
Why'd you have an evil laugh?
I don't know, I just feel evil.
You would be evil together?
Uh, sure.
Sure.
So
Someone got a bot to say kick page and it's like there's like the fifth account that is
They're so unpaid for that. Oh my god. What did you
What's my name, what's my name
Do you need bacon? Do you need
pork? I have I have a pepperoni as a pepperoni and I have a hot honey pepperoni um subway.
I'm not sure if that's for is as a pepperoni pork. No, let me see my dog. Muffy. What is
it buddy? We're muffy. What's wrong buddy? Damn rags. Come on. What is it boy?
Uh-oh, you have neither, but you and you're typing the same you're typing the same names in the chat like
So you're a doc since you so don't do so complete your comment, please
Oh
I mean, it's not even worth it. I don't know. It's just some bot has been it's been
Let's get down on all fours, you know, sorry, let's get down to the point. I'm sorry. Okay
Well
Joker you're still gonna come visit me in California someday and we're gonna hold hands up on the go out of the pier
Me and you we're gonna go to no jumper
Yeah, we're going to do that.
Adam 22. Yeah, so what we're
going to do is we're going to
get you jumped in to the
curves, right? And then we're
going to, uh, we're going to
let you be a gay group
brother and then I'm going to
get you on the jumper. And
then I'll let you like, uh,
your, your side kid. Yeah.
Okay. And then what we do is
we, uh, you fight Krip Mack.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay. You're a Krip Mack.
Yeah, but he's a I'm a creep. I'm a creep. I guess
We'll get you with some boxing gloves on and you just have to take you know, despite of this you can
Then we get all the money, you know, you might get a little hurt, but you know
Like it will hurt I mean
What are you asking me sir, as you can see there's smoke coming out of my microphone.
Would you do a threesome with the crib back at myself and Joker?
We can have us some chocolate it'd be like it would be like it'd be like a vanilla Oreo with the chocolate in the middle
They said get some tea you say you don't have any tea
He doesn't he doesn't have teeth though. That was here. I still have teeth. I have teeth.
Give me a girl.
The cycle rate can store on his teeth. I still have teeth.
I hear Joker's getting fatter. Yeah, Joker's getting fatter, maybe.
Well
Joker, do you still like me anymore or do you like my kind of a joke to you now?
Very nice
I
Actually one of those things that should be like instantly you say
Hey, no, you're like, no, I like I like love you
And then I'm gonna say oh I have to think about it for a few days and like, you know, I don't know
There's moments where there are moments there are moments where some of the guests in your show. I can't
Sometimes I'll watch the show. It'll be really fun. I'll be really entertaining. That's what I watch and it's like
Just
It's a hit or miss. You know saying like it's not always
Just some of the people are just crazy though. It's like
Not even crazy. It's just like boring. Sorry. I mean it's not you. It's just telling you
It's boring. It's boring. It's crazy. They're boring. I don't know. It's like
It's hard to listen to people argue and okay, we're going for like an hour, you know, yeah, I know I know it's hard
It's fun for like a minute or two
It's like, whoa, did you see these did you see flirty diamond and you hear flirty diamond and raging demon are already are together now
No, I wouldn't surprise me
And she's
she's what she doesn't even like
Hardly remembers you she's like really it's a region team and they're watching titanic together and he sent her a dick pic and
Everyone's seeing his his little demon work. I would say what we call it everybody
His wiener
Like one like that
So, but you know, so, but were you in love with 30 diamond ever or was it always we just playing with her heart? I
was just
Yeah, we're only fans here on the podcast. Let's see what's on there and I want on there. It's like
Milk coming out of a man's manboob doesn't like make any sense. Like you definitely poured milk on yourself
You know, it's like it's like obvious like
She's like trying to can he's trying to convince you well
He's a woman by pouring milk on his chest to pretend like he is a woman having breast milk
So people buy his only fans, but he is really a
Man says that it's just
Why does everyone talk to you're talking about weird accusations in the chat Tiffany wears t-shirts is here
Tiffany are your friends is diggy. He said he was saying he loves you and you're awesome
And are you good with him? Let's make sure he was up. I don't hate anybody. There's like a few people on here
They're insufferable, and it's not sticky. I'll tell you
Not so you okay
Yeah, I'm not talking about me really. It's not you. It's not anybody that turns their cameras on it's always like the you know, it's always those
People that just want to like
But it hasn't been like that lately except actually no earlier you had a whole game on their mind
What did Aldi do what did Aldi? Did he go crazy?
There's croak here, I don't I haven't seen croak in a long time. Well
You're welcome on the panel.
Anybody here?
I hope everyone's doing great today.
Yeah, I was out of truth. Halfway to have natives before the color card. Yep. It's like page pages
These are those we can't got in those two hate me just like to oh, yeah, so you look I'd say he was he was he was just trying to
Was that I'm sorry. I'm sorry. They're using your I deleted that stream. I don't it's not right to you
You may be fun of you or
Those guys are pretty cool
Because you know that I see like Tiffany or teacher. She looks like a lovely person and it's like not nice to
You're making fun of her. She's you know, nobody knows anybody's story or it already is
No
Okay, so I hope you're okay
Hey, spunky you gonna retire from the chat six years of chatting way of panels today a long time
Yeah, so that's what I understand. I understand well
You know
You know, it's like sometimes you can't get old
I'm just I'm kind of enjoying it. Yeah, it's always always new stuff. I got a new uh, I got some new babes
What kind of baby you got? I got babes everywhere. Maybe they
Yeah, but
Grape haze
In that great cool a mile. Hey, am I
Just a prank bro, just a prank. It's a prank
Yeah, that's what they're saying they're saying that if I was like that I would like
Sleep in the bed with you and then if somebody like caught me I would just say it's a prank
Yeah
It is. It is. It is. It is.
I would definitely break him so
break him so hard. He'd prank
yourself. Yeah. Are you going to prank me sometimes, Joker?
No, I'm not going to prank you. Joker prank me. He's like, he's like, I want to come
and I want to, I want to come to every don do and I want to come.
I do what I want to do. I just have to I graduate
Got your real school
Graduated you graduated from there graduate congratulations
But now one day I'll go out there, I don't know this gonna be like is that we're gonna be like
Sometime in the next couple months. I'm gonna go out. It's like ball. It's so hot ish
Like before winter doesn't go
I was gonna go to LA
I was thinking about going on like it's a vacation to Australia
Yeah, well
Do you want to go down under I?
Mean I heard is like the best place to have a great barrier reef
You know they have Sydney for the opera houses and go watch them like I can watch a bunch of dudes put on like
Wakes, you know like the like the 1800s
you know, like when they have like those white wigs on their head and they put on the makeup because in the opera
It's only male actors. So the males have to play all the female roles
So they have to dress up like a woman in drag
Well, that's what the sorry that used to be the then they changed it in 60s
I don't think so
It used to be that women couldn't be actors until they have a yeah
Yeah, but that was you know, that could Shakespeare's I wasn't like, you know during the opera they've happily
No reason to lie about being married unless you're an illegal man. Hmm. So cool. Never move out. Okay
So let's leave Joker alone, let's like not I'll make fun of Joker's. He's a great guy
I'm sorry say I didn't mean to graduate on my sorry
I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I don't I
Uh, sorry, what'd you say mr. Big Types?
Mr.. Big Types
They said my mic is trash wait, which I have a fan on if my fan might be messing it up
I have this mic, and then I have a different mic
Hello ladies and gentlemen, it is your home, so it's the best cycle we can stare
Whoo
Whoa
I think it's down. It's really good. It's not I like the hot honey. It was actually kind of sweet, but
We just sleep at full time though. It's a big pipes for 24 hours
For $1200. Yeah, probably
I've been probably annoyed to death, but
If I survive, I'll have a 1200 bucks
In today's news, we have heat advisories across the nation site. How many degrees is it for your app?
Like by the 80 degrees, I don't know
80 degrees 100 and 100 degrees in Georgia
Hundred degrees over there. Are you sweating? Why don't you take off your your shirt and pants?
You met Dougie. Oh cool. Dougie is awesome
Yeah, there's good people like Dougie and like, you know, Jamie Cowboys, He-Man
Nick, you know
I
What's wrong with you, buddy
I'm gonna say hi to cycle it might be over there. See you
That's you boy look it's here. You're just a little muffy look down
She's big and strong
Joe can we crack if he was walking the streamers that's your big pressure 24 hours. Yeah, I mean I cracked just be on the panel
With them for a few hours. I he like drove me insane
Many of any person he didn't he took me said he hexed me
And he says
Mr. Big five so definitely like where you out here. He'll talk to you for
And he was like
That's anyway that I smelled batters would do like that and then he's the one peeing in it in a jug in a corner of his room
Ready you go outside we go play
All you want to go outside we're gonna side
Tell me tell me boy. Tell me we're gonna sign
Oh
I
Okay, I have fun. Thank you. Love you, Joker. Okay, I
Don't know guys
Let's come off. I think I'm yeah, the link is posted
Yeah
Yeah, he got if I was Saints
You guys know state 10 state 10 is pretty cool, so I'll have to go to get some
Probably drinks and some more tobacco. Oh, I'm putting tobacco actually, but
Down the guys are annoying as hell. Yeah
Hi, babe. Hi
Mr. Taylor had recently started chatting here. Yeah. Well, everyone introduce yourself, you know, you know, we if you're a nice person
No, say hi to the Mars, you know. Hi
Yep, the calm down. I know
Well, I don't know. It was well on the shot. Hey, Jamie's cowboy. Say hi
Make sure you say hi to everybody Jamie because there's a lot of new people here
And I know you're so friendly and you know warm and makes people feel welcome. Hey everybody. Welcome to my show
Um, yeah, I'm trying to get a big ratio of minimum. It is 55 people in the chat. Wow. That's awesome. It's been off for about almost an hour
Hey Joker
Hey here, thank you gang you guys for sharing the uh sharing my links and stuff. This is getting dirty. What's getting dirty?
Okay age stop smoke break time
Yeah, I'll talk to you
Is your pen in or is it like like is a weed one?
Yeah, oh
It's so slow tomorrow's gonna be an insanely busy though. We have like two huge events tomorrow
Hi, what's up, baby? How are you doing?
Good. I guess Paige is talking to her daughter. I'm doing pretty good.
We're just hanging out this afternoon. I just had a
Thrust in my sandwich
and I got a pizza bagel and
Just take it easy
Yeah, and it's been a yeah in the a page I'm back sorry I had to
Yeah, it works. Tell you are you a worker? No
But I'm on my break right now Grace came to work with me. Oh, yeah
Oh, you see what kind of work you do? I work at a golf course and I do everything here anything
Yeah, that's cool. Yeah, it's super slow today because the weather shit, but oh well
There's lots to do usually I gotta like do some cart maintenance and a little bit here, but
let's vote it
kitchen prep for tomorrow
that was cute little car girls that go around
there
that's her
I do that too, I love it
you usually go out and get things like you bought with them
they'll buy you drinks for after work or whatever
Yeah, it's not a huge like fancy golf course, but it's not a shitty one and it's like more laid back for sure
It's not like coity-toity, but it's you make pretty good money here
And it's gonna be a long weekend this weekend. So we have campers out here too. So it'll be nice
We have a campground here too
That's my favorite kind of place in life, like not hoity-toity, but not trashy, in a race of it all.
Yeah, middle-class shit, middle-class shit.
Yeah, absolutely. Those people are so down to earth and cool.
Yeah, I agree.
It's like, I don't like rich people, but I like billionaires.
Billionaires are down to earth too, believe it or not, but like...
I'm too poor for rich people to like me. It's not like I don't like them.
So they were snotty, but like whatever.
Aw.
I'm just I don't know my poverty line. Want to take you to town? No, I can't drive to town right now
What do you want to go to town for?
I might work. I can't right now after
Yeah, but I had
Well, yeah, be your mom so yeah
Americans can't just say what they mean yes, that's a man
Think he's in here. I think he was kind of have problems
Then JT was kind of causing a problem JT put up some some of these reality or something like a picture of like a
Dog mounting a woman or it's like kind of like a dog woman giving a rottweiler piggyback ride
But I don't I don't know what that picture was about
So it was kind of strange
Yeah, well my wife JT was that JT. Why did you post that for me? Hey? Yeah, and that yeah
Plus there were a pretty big deep in a picture of somebody up in the chat
She's in the chat right now. Hi a dog duct tape to it and naked woman. Oh, it's not disgusting
Guys, why would you put that on my shirt? That is like I hate that it's like
DC I might have to thank you for doing that
It's sort of like crystal good. Yeah
I think totally crystal is good, you know look at look up
You know Google the crystal and like look at the look at the benefits and like really to take seriously where you place it as
What you need it for?
Yeah, I know I deleted it. I deleted it. Tiffany. It was
You guys I will be back later. I gotta go. Okay. Bye. Okay. Yeah page has to go
Yeah, but it was pretty pretty disgusting. I don't know why
People continue to try to put sneak that stuff on my show. It's like fortunately I was okay
But it was pretty pretty bolder. I mean it did take me a while to like understand what I was looking at the figure
It was pretty hard to see but
How's everyone do Jamie's Cowboys, yeah Jamie's Cowboys and he man or holding down the chat is mobs
I'm glad I didn't get a strike.
Yeah, thank you.
I mean, it's like, I go, and, you know,
I appreciate if anybody, that happens to anybody.
Just come to me first.
You know, I'll probably be like,
I can delete the episode.
I can make sure it doesn't happen again,
but I need to know, oh, this is me,
they're using the picture of,
and I don't want it on the show.
That kind of thing.
I don't want people to be harassed and that kind of stuff.
So just let me know first.
I'm not trying to condone it.
I'm not trying to like, it'll be just funny.
I don't think it's part of my show.
I don't know if people are doing it.
Remember to the bad mom. Oh, no
Yeah, it's not your channel, you don't want to
That's okay. Yeah, I know he man. Oh
The mods sometimes, you know have a bad day or get annoyed. So, you know, just don't piss off the mods. I'll say
So are you there spunky?
Yeah, I'm here
Yeah
Well, why would GT do that though like why would he put up like that kind of why would he have that kind of photo in the first place?
They ever have like an animal. I don't know GT well enough, but he's probably just showing off and you know trying to be cool for his friends and
You know ride the line of like fucking your channel is is really amusing to some people and you know
That's what he was doing. That's that's the the joy that he gets out of that
Right well, I don't know. It's like kind of like what nobody of my yeah
I'm kind of at my expense and then there's like then he wouldn't have this platform
Jever talk I was let him talk and like hang out and be part of the group and everything and he's like gonna try to
Do things that hurt my channel. I anybody does
Yeah, I have to watch out because I do have people that they don't pretend to be my friend and then we'll want to like
He tries to get panels taken down. Yeah, okay channels and panels. Yeah, I tried to charm his way back in
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah, I mean, you know, it's all a game to most people on the internet.
They don't feel like there's any real consequences to it.
So it's, you know, it's hilarious to them.
But to you, you're making money off of it probably.
And, you know, this is a lifeline for you.
And it's, it's a, you know, it means a lot to you.
But people, it's just a, you know, it's a fuck around playground.
Yeah, I have to like, you know, but it's my fault, you know, for not, you know, for falling asleep and for, you know.
Yeah, but I'll have to protect you protect what's yours, you know. Yeah. Yeah
You need to cherish these old
Old people to post my check. Hi. Bye guys. Hey, my Nicole. Thank you for participating in the I know Nicole is one of the top
Top fans of the show
I got a lot of people here all over Jabroni
Yeah, well kind of like
Let's just like shake things up a little bit. Let's do a
Oh
If anyone else feels you know feels we did like to
Participate we can do this like I like when I
Can give back to the to the chat
It's not working.
What are you trying to do?
I was trying to give to membership, but it's not working.
Okay, if it doesn't work right now, I'll try to gift it later.
Yeah, I'll try to give to membership.
I've had like probably 20 gifted memberships in the past couple of days.
It's still exciting.
But I'd like to see some more familiar people get some.
And so we'll see what happens.
Try to get a couple
How many members do you have now I think oh, I think like almost I got hundred
Okay, look, I think I did I think I did it
Almost a hundred I think
Maybe maybe less maybe less, but it's increased. I mean in the first month
There's a lot of gifted memberships and so of course they just think about there wasn't a lot and then now there's a lot of work
There's some more gifted memberships happening. There we go
That's really cool. There we go, so I give to the membership it was received the vexed
vexed students receive the membership and so
You know people that receive the memberships. They I don't know if I recognize the vexed students or you're in chat, but
It's fun when people give memberships and
Receives them very generous very generous donations
Also, if you guys are reading I got reading it today for you. You know, yes
Oh, yeah, Jamie doing some money today uses for some memberships. I don't know. I bought a couple of memberships from that one
so yeah
There's a lot of a lot of
Other new members and stuff and also make sure you take that with gifted membership at the top and make sure you're opted in
To receive a gifted membership because you have to opt in you have to say like I want to receive
Gifted memberships. I think you can get there by clicking that you get to the top of the thing
So how are we doing guys?
what made you want to get into this like what inspired you like one day you woke up and you're
like i'm gonna i'm gonna do this oh yeah i've been wanting to do for a long time and it's like you know
of course I grew up on Howard Stern and then I also like to socialize online. I was always just
too shy to be on camera but I was doing terror readings on Etsy and then everything kind of
moved to YouTube. I started watching terror readers on YouTube. I thought that's a great
platform to be able to work from home, do readings and have a show and I've always wanted to do it
just to go long time to get started. I started like last year probably about nine months ago.
And so now this show is like, you know,
turning into, yeah, I got 15 people in the chat right now.
I got, you know, a lot of members, got a great mods.
I hope, I do hope that some of the members will show up
and say hi and shout out.
Yo, there's an accent, they look right there.
It's an accent, thank you for the membership.
Oh, you're welcome.
Yeah, you got your reward of the membership.
That's awesome.
So now Dixon has access to a lot of the,
Lot of the videos that put behind the scenes, you know, like there's a lot of shows that are getting a little spicy for and
and
There's some emojis all get there's a
You get your name in green and it's a fun way to support the show
But yeah, I know I just I'm very
Inspired by a lot of content creators. I think it's a great platform. I like really
I've met so many wonderful people here.
You know, it's just fun.
It's just, you know, it's just, it's fun.
Some people just do it for fun.
I kind of take it more seriously as a business
because I want to like be able to, you know,
support myself with this channel.
So, um.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And hopefully, I will entertain enough people.
I think I'm still very much starting out.
I just have 2,555 subscribers, I think,
which is kind of like, you know, kind of low.
That's the beginning.
Yeah.
We're gonna start somewhere. Yeah, it just it just slowed down a little bit because it's been like a few weeks
It's but I am getting like the 20,000 of viewing hours a month or watch time a month
20,000 hours. That's pretty awesome. You know, that's pretty amazing. Yeah
Even if you learn subscribing they are coming and watching your shit. Yeah, and
Yeah, I told Elisa's or Donna that I'm with you know, Lisa, but yes, she was pretty impressed that she's like you think yes
So you're doing pretty good. Like yeah, she helps you actually help me she helped me promote my show
Yeah, I haven't been over to her chat a little bit because her chat doesn't like me anymore
I just don't want to bother her right now, but if I can't I'm gonna go to Florida sort of
There's something I would love to do that. But I want to be pretty much
She doesn't del Rey a bokeh and West Palm Beach. I think it's your hurry. I'm originally from Cocoa Beach, Florida
Which is like East of Orlando like on the coast
uh-huh
Yeah, well my brother is from slow my brother-in-law's from Florida and like you know, and then I'm you know, Oliver
I think it's in Florida. There's a lot of people in the chat from Florida too. So you're from Coco. You were born there
That's awesome. Yeah, I grew up in Cocoa Beach. Yeah, I went to Cocoa Beach High and that was a long-ass time ago, but
Well, I grew up in kind of a beach city like in California like, you know,
the beach cities and so my school was like right on the cliffs next to the
ocean and stuff and it was a pretty nice setting to grow up in.
Did you guys do the thing where you would all just kind of like walk out of class and go to the beach for the day
and there's nothing I can do about it?
Yeah, sometimes we would always go smoke on the cliffs and we walked down to the rocks and stuff like that
It's called Rat Beach
It's called Torrance. It's called right after Torrance. It's Rat Beach, Torrance Beach, Redondo Beach, and then it goes
Hermosa Beach, Manhattan Beach, and then it goes down to Venice Beach.
Yeah, my work wife is from Redondo Beach.
That's where I live in Redondo, so I go to the Redondo Pier and I'm right in Redondo.
It's a nice place, it's a very nice place and I go to the pier a lot.
I like to go to the pier and go in the, can you share your ranch?
I don't know, Jamie, what are you thinking?
The pier is beautiful, yeah, we have fun on the pier.
haven't seen you there yet so I can't wait until you go yeah I'll have to go
soon let me see well it's 505 now yeah so I love on Friday we have a special
Friday but I don't know I think if I fear the best to talk with in the world I
think it does that this is a bit this is the biggest fish market in in California
is your daughter beach so
Yeah, so I go I go to for fish taco that I've everything I've eaten there the fish taco. Thank you Christine
Thank you so much. Christine. Christine is good to the membership
We received his membership
All right, I'm gonna let you go. I'm actually
Love you good talking to you
I'm gonna talk to you too. I'm pulling up to Justin's house. Okay. Say hi. I will. Have a good night.
Have a good night. Talk to you soon. Bye.
Yeah, it's time. I've got a membership. Congratulations, time. You're now one of
Psyche's Angels. You know, especially, I want to draw all my angels too. I have already drawn a
But yeah. Let me see my picture of time I've drawn. Let's see. I'll put it right to it.
There he is. He's celebrating his membership. Yes.
Tiffany, thank you for the super sticker. Thank you so much. Yeah
Are you are you are you floaty diamonds?
Not my best
Diamonds
Elbow your elbow the elbow. Oh my gosh, I know
That's for yours
Lucky to the week. Thank you. What if I open right here? I'm Jamie's Cowboys here
I need to go on it. I don't like it
He said, don't show, how do you say show yours?
Thank you so much for the super chat. Very sweet of you. Thank you Tiffany, I like that red super sticker.
Hi Summer, I'm sorry, I'm sorry for missing anybody coming in. How are you guys? Come on up.
I have, I have, I have somewhere to draw, oh Christine.
Hello. Hey, that's kind of why everything's calmed down and people weren't up here because um
I really wanted to talk to you yesterday and now that it's calm. Maybe you want to talk to me?
Okay, okay, because I was really I was really really upset yesterday. What happened?
Well, I'm gonna you were right here with us all
Okay. And I understand that when there's drama and people going at people that upset you a little bit and you kind of shut down, I get it.
And that's why you should have good mods to help you out. But a couple of things did.
Blurty diamond has some done some really horrible things on these YouTube streets and
yesterday when she was up here and it she showed he showed a picture of video that
He created of AI
Summer and I kiss him now. It's AI generated
It's inappropriate
and she can get into this. I know. I took it down. I took it down. I mean, I know. I mean, I can't
control what people put on the screen sometimes. Hey, who else can say how you can? You can. It's
your channel. And see, I'm, and I'm going to tell you something. Other channels have been taken down
because the channel owner is doing exactly what you're doing. You can't control. No, that's wrong,
It's your channel. You were supposed to control it. Hey, honey
But but what I'm trying and I'm trying to talk to you in a calm tone
Okay, it's okay. So here because I was furious yesterday
I'm not chicken cakes
Well, I'm not her
They're not chicken cakes. No, I'm not the Sun's like her sweetheart. That's what I've been told. My name is Christine
Hey, Christine
Hello, I'm not chicken cakes though. Christine. I just turned 30 May 2nd. Well, happy birthday
What's up? What's up? Christine? What's up?
Okay
Can you do me one moment sir, can you just let me finish one minute with site, please?
You're about to finish. Yes, just one minute with them
Just one minute, honey, you're about to orgasm right now for real
No, I'm about to cut a head off you said you're about to finish I am I'm about to cut a head off
If you can just give me one more moment, please
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir
You know, I had I handle myself
Yes, we I'll be happy to speak with you after
Yes
Thank you
And I can handle myself and most everybody else can but I'll be honest with you
So we're gonna be able to talk doctor and like when when did you join when did you join like the panels and stuff like that?
Just now today's your first day. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, I've been here for months and months
So, you know psyche for a long time. I do
What do you both both of you guys believe in?
Okay, give me a moment and I'll share that with you, but it's like what flirty diamond has done is
So wrong on so many levels. I know it's like I thought you like a real man here unlike Audi
Thank you, but you need to be aware
You you saying you are not responsible. You are your channel owner. The other thing is through the night
You had some really horrible stuff going on in your chat and on panel, and I know you've been aware of this
I'm surprised your panel still here after that
Yeah, maybe when you're tired and the screen when you're tired, so yeah
Yeah, your chat was handled well, but nobody could help with the panel
Yeah, I don't know I just needed to get this out, but psych you need to figure things out my dear
Thank You sweetheart
Okay, how's it going Joe?
You're letting evil people up here when you're sleeping. They're fucking taking advantage of y'all day long
100% it's like your real life when you fall asleep. You got to get advantage of psyche. Don't lick your lips. Don't you dare?
And you can't cover your head up especially with what happened just after noon it's already diamond. You just can't
your head in the band oh
What if what did I mean do?
Well, first of all that AI videos you showed
That's huge psych
Well, I mean no one everyone knows it's not really you and some it doesn't matter not everybody does people don't know me
How does it look is it realistic or no? Yeah
Yes, yeah, okay, and I'm gonna tell you something. I love summer. You know that I have no problem kissing summer
If I did this in real life, I wouldn't mind it. It's an AI generated
That's kind of
It's kind of hot. Well, thanks Joe. We're kind of hot. We're kind of hot for old people, okay?
That's kind of a joke, or just to get the kids to discord. Oh my gosh.
Well, even what Flirty Diamond did to Raging Demon.
And then he tried, he tried, um, telling Kate he'll give, uh, a video of Joker jacking off if he let, if Kate lets him back into her discord.
Now, come on. What kind of person does that?
Yeah.
That's, that's not a good person.
That's not a beautiful person.
That's a mean evil person
Yeah, I know so
Cypress cave
Big dog start about that
Fuck oh, we got way. We got Joe. Hey, man. Yeah, the bestiality was pretty bad
No, but it's got like a squirrel in your chin or something Chris. I don't know if you know that it's like a little great thing
Wait a minute
There's like a cheese it I've seen a cheese it in there. There's like a clean it out for Joe. Get on tell him clean it up
But no you want to sit and enchant be a bully perfect man up
Wait, who's being a bully in that chat Christine tell me right now. Would you booty go booty go booty go? Yeah, booty go
Now they changed it to booty goon. Joe, you know me dog. Anyway, I've got to go
He's like oh Joe's a drunk idiot or whatever so fuck you buster
You see
Orioles we got the Orioles that you're your iconic a fuck it over black
Hey, they fucking they didn't even get in the fucking playoffs in the fucking
Yeah, we're losing three to nothing right now we're getting our ass kicked. Oh, you want to batter up?
You were getting the other by your girlfriend already that's why you left all batter up Chris. There he goes
Let me see your baddest thing. Oh
He got the bat little crowbar little crowbar
I love that video of you and
Are you going to end it or don't even end it you can't get in trouble. What the hell?
What the hell is oh he's gonna swing batter batter a